MANASWANI

PANDA Finance Expert ,DPMU,Odisha

(8 Years of Experience)

F&A professional with 8 years of experience in various field of accounting, finance & administrations. I am a Self-motivated and hardworking individual, presently looking for a challenging opportunity to prove my skills and to nourish my knowledge.



manaswanipanda18@gmail.com

7978475727

At-Sarlakani Near Christ Jyoti Bhawan, PO-Dhankauda Pin-768006, Sambalpur, Odisha, India



WORK EXPERIENCE

Junior Officer, Finance & Accounts

Aditya Aluminium (A unit of Hindalco Industries Ltd.)

08/2014 - 05/2016

Tasks

 Involved in Accounts payable, Inventory Management, Internal costings, Funds projection and have a experience of working in ORACLE 11i

Assistant Project Director Finance & Microfinance(Credit)

District Rural Development Agency

10/2016 - 06/2017

District Rural Development Agency, Sundargarh Govt. of Orissa

Tasks

 Worked as project in charge of OLM, Monitoring SHG Bank Linkage, Disbursement of funds to SHG, finance activity under OLM, Payable, Receivables & recovery management, implementation of different financial projects, regular audit of block accounts, allocation of funds, collection of utilization certificate, fund projection of DRDA.

Finance expert

District Planning and Monitoring unit

07/2017 - Present

District Planning and Monitoring unit, Balangir Govt. of Orissa

Tasks

 Involved in preparation of Annual Action plan, Analytical support, Financial planning of the district, Planning Sanctioning Releasing and Monitoring of district funds, Developing MPRs for developmental and infrastructure projects. Liasioning with various executive agencies.

EDUCATION

IRPM

Sambalpur university

2019 - 2022

LLB

Sambalpur university

2016 - 2018 57.23

MBA (Finance and marketing)

Sambalpur university

2012 - 2014 7.75

B.Com

Sambalpur university

2009 - 2012 67.60

SKILLS

Efficient in MS Word & MS Excel

Good communication skill

Efficient decision making

Toam loados Einansia

inancial Analyst

Vendor Management

SLA Execution

Audit

Making DPRs In Large Projects

Cross Functional Collaberation

Reporting & Documentation

Budgeting Forecasting

A&F , Business Administration

Reconciliation

RECOGNITION

Achievements in

HINDALCO & DPMU Odisha

- 2 times gold medalist in the university examination for MBA (Finance) & for IRPM
- Rewarded with best employee award in HINDALCO
- Submitted a DPR of MLALD scheme to bring efficiency and innovation to DPMU, which was highly appreciated
- Successfully Implemented 5T program which improved the TAT in project approval by 22.00 % & Financial Sanction by 18 % in FY 2020-21

INTERESTS

Community work Trekking

Reading Cycling